When making a lantern sleeve, we need to lengthen the sleeve so that it has enough fabric to make the folds pile up.
Select the outer line of the sleeve bottom and set the inner line of the lining. After cutting the seam allowance, you can get the sleeve opening.
Here you need to cut the seam allowance, select the top and bottom two straight lines and then you can align them.
Shrink the sleeve opening, so that the folds pile up on the sleeve opening.
Use 100% of the seam allowance on the sleeve opening and the seam allowance.
You can keep the length of the original line so that it is not easy to be stretched.
Next, I used the plus point division tool to add a center point in the sleeve.
When using the plus point division tool, click on the mouse button on the line and you can set the length and proportion in the fold window.
Using the extension tool extension sheet can make the sheet more flexible.
If you have more fabric, you can fold it up after you have enough fabric.
Click on the straight line of the sleeve and then extend it all the way to the line that needs to be extended.
Click on the middle line of the extension and you can open the sheet from the middle to both sides.
Pull the sleeve a little higher to maintain the original curve and ensure that the sleeve and the sleeve length are unified.
Since there are not enough folds at the moment, you still need to use the extension tool to extend the sheet again.
To match the length of the sleeve and the length of the sleeve, and continuously shrink the width of the sleeve, make the top small and the bottom large.
Use the edit point line tool to activate the center point after selecting the middle line. You can use the center point as the center point.
Change a pose for the model.
To make the fold naturally downward.
After selecting the sleeve sheet, open the triangle next to the pressure, apply a pressure value of 0.3 for it to make it more loose.
When making the shoulder sleeve, we need to make a long strip of the shoulder.
Click on the 3D strip.
In the 2D window, we can determine the position according to the blue position point.
After confirming the position, we can draw a inner line and set the inner line of the shoulder.
After selecting the inner line, align it to the outer line of the strip, then cut and sew it to make a long strip of the strip.
Remove the strip of the shoulder to show the model's shoulder.
After selecting the long strip of the shoulder, freeze it to avoid instability in the subsequent modification of other strips.
Use the extension tool to extend the strip of the sleeve part to make it have more fabric and folds.
Adjust the curve after extension to make it more smooth.
Está listo.
¡¡¡Buen Provecho!!!
Thank you.
You
you
when making shouze
I will first choose the platform of the sleeve
then set the interval and the number of the inner line
to create a number of inner lines
when choosing alas технологi
We can create the line
on the inside of the curve
inside of the curve
Add a vertical inner line in the middle of the board, and then select it to cut and sew it.
After selecting the inner line, align it to the outer line of the board and add points.
After using the extension tool, we can extend the board point by point according to the straight line just added, so that the extension can ensure that the extension part is equal.
When extending, we can also set the angle and distance in the spring when we click on the right mouse button.
You can see that the extension board has a gap in the 3D window,
so we need to re-arrange the board.
When arranging the board, try to ensure that the board does not intersect with the model arm.
Next, I will delete some uneven points and straight points on the board to make the board curve smoother.
After selecting the straight point on the curve, turn it into a curve point.
Apply elasticity to the outer line of the board and reduce the proportion of the elasticity to make the effect of the draw.
The lower the value, the more obvious the effect of the draw.
Apply elasticity to the outer line of the board inside the sleeve and reduce the proportion to make the draw.
If there is a relationship between a точно
andordnung board
When making non-sew, we can delete the original board and then create a long strip board.
Use the rectangular tool to click the 2D window.
In the spring window, we can enter the width of the board.
Then sew the long strip of the sleeve board to the hemline.
Use the plus point division tool to add a straight line at the center of the sleeve bottom.
Then shorten the height of the two sides of the board to adjust the shape of the board in the 3D window.
Adjust the curve to make the edge of the sleeve as round as possible.
Apply 100 elasticity to the hemline to prevent it from being stretched by the sleeve board.
Adjust the height of the board to make the shape of the sleeve in the 3D window as short as possible.
Adjust the height of the board to make the shape of the sleeve in the 3D window as long as possible.
Extend the length of the sleeve to create more creases.
Adjust the length of the sleeve to create more creases.
When making hulu embroidery, I will first create a few vertical internal lines according to the curve line and sew them into a few pieces of board slices after making a horizontal internal line.
After selecting the internal lines, align the internal lines to the board slices and add points.
By adding vertical lines, separate the upper and lower lines, so that we can adjust the bottom lines separately.
After selecting the board slices at the bottom, set the internal lines and align them to the board slices and add points.
After selecting the horizontal lines on the same side, move them to the left and right respectively, and widen the board slices at the bottom.
After selecting the horizontal lines, turn them into free-loving boards.
Now we can see that the board's curve line is not very natural.
We can use the adjustment point tool to make the curve line adjustment smoother.
The curve line is too wide, so we need to shorten the length of the curve board.
After selecting the external lines of the board slices, select the length to change in the right-click menu, and you can change the length of the lines.
When you change the length, you can change the direction.
Here, we select both, and shorten from both sides to the middle.
Create a long board as the curve, and sew the sleeves on the curve.
Since the board is too small, the grid surface is less, and it will be interlocked with the model.
You can reduce the diameter of the particle, so that there are more grid spaces.
Use the free-loving tool to sew the sleeves and the curve.
When sewing the sleeves, press the Shift key to sew multiple boards.
After deleting the original sewing lines, divide the vertical lines into sections, and sew the upper and lower parts of the board separately.
Use a sewing machine to sew the front and back of the board.
After selecting the seam lines of the lower part of the board, you can set a folding angle of the foam line to fold it outward.
After hardening, the folding effect is more obvious.
After completing one side of the production, we can delete the original and then align it to the other side.
When making the speaker sleeve, we need to make sure that the bottom plate is wide enough, so now we will first draw the inner line to separate the upper and lower parts.
After cutting and sewing, use the extension tool to open the bottom plate to make it wider and have enough fabric.
Being more explosive than this part, now the top plate has spread out, we can make sure that the emerged for theavoir.
Sert the top plate with a double-sided tape.
Now our top plate has been made for theauric.
However, you can notice that the current component does not have a conflict effect, so we need to open the component conflict.
The component conflict is the MD11 new function, which will be simulated after arranging the version, to avoid interruption with the component.
Since the bottom of the sleeve is not wide enough, we still need to use the extension tool to make the sleeve wider.
To replace a softer fabric for the clothing, here we use wool.
After selecting the outer line of the side seam, you can generate the inner line according to the curve line,
then use the fold-over-folding tool to set the folding angle for the inner line.
After hardening, the folding effect will be more obvious.
Due to the current fold of the elbow part is too hard, and there is too much fabric, we need to narrow the middle part a little.
The cutины of the upper edges of the sleeve and slits are slightly
separated, so it does not
center on the hemline.
For the bottom panel, we designed a Eduwa-like problem.
This is from Eduwa, Third 2.0, the 3D model used by Great Native Paramijd imagem heみ
After where I reduced the nuevo 곶 , I'll fold this line to someone's inner corner, and now cut this line from the middle to the收 couple.
After the change, we need to re-set the inner line and apply the fold angle to re-create the fold effect.
After creating one side, we align it to the other side.
After selecting the outer line of the side seam, the inner line is created according to the curve line, and the fold angle of the inner line can be adjusted in the fold window.
When making the shoulder sleeve, we need to cut the sheet in the position of the sleeve.
Then use the extension tool to extend the inner line to the sheet.
When extending, click on the mouse and right-click in the fold window to set the distance and angle. Try to ensure that the extension distance is consistent.
Apply a new fabric to the shoulder sleeve.
The fabric will be more rigid when the fold angle is increased. The shoulder sleeve will also be more rigid.
Turn the straight line point into a curve point and delete the uneven curve point.
If we still want to make the shoulder more rigid, we can adjust the curve of the sleeve to a larger curve.
Apply a more rigid leather fabric to the shoulder sleeve.
The other sheets can use wool-like fabrics to make some soft and hard changes.
After selecting the sewing line, it can set the fold angle, and it can manually control the pivot angle of the shoulder shoulder.
At the time of making the leg sleeves, I will raise the sleeves, so that the sleeves have enough fabric to stack and fold.
At the same time, I will lengthen the sleeves overall.
Then, select the outer line of the plate on both sides, and create a vertical inner line line according to the curve.
Then use the internal multi-edging tool to draw a line inside.
When drawing, click the mouse button to set the mirror in the window.
After selecting the inner line, you can set the inner line diameter to it, and align the inner line to the outer line of the plate.
After selecting the vertical inner line, cut it and sew it.
After deleting the plate on the right side, align a new piece of the plate, so that it is aligned with the information.
This allows us to modify the link between the plates.
Then use the extension tool to click the inner line and extend the plate.
When extending, right-click and enter the extension distance to ensure that the distance of each extension is the same.
After the extension is completed, we need to adjust the curve and straight line points that are not smooth enough, so that the line section becomes smooth.
Then adjust the excess of the curve to make it smoother.
Now we need to adjust the懸垂, the arc, the curve and the arc line.
This requires us to adjust the slender ends of the curve.
We need to adjust the slender ends of the curve, so that the size of the line will be defined.
We will adjust the length of the line and turn the light-discharge button to the left side of the line.
Then adjust the length of the line and turn the light-discharge button to the right side of the line.
In order to have more folds in the position of the sleeve, it is necessary to raise the sleeve up a little.
After adding a straight line at the position of the sleeve, divide the line into two sections, then select the outer line of the sleeve and the outer line of the sleeve and apply elasticity for it.
Reduce the proportion of elasticity to reduce the effect of making folds.
After changing the model posture, I will insert a model made from the outside as a component.
Use the component to support the part of the costume sleeve.
But we can notice that the component has no conflict effect, so we need to select the component and open the component conflict in the property editor.
You can notice that the part of the costume sleeve is held up.
If you need more folds, you can reduce the proportion of elasticity again.
Reduce the proportion of elasticity to reduce the effect of making folds.
After reducing the proportion of elasticity, the details will be richer.
Align the made sleeves to the other side.
Next, I will introduce the production method of two fold-and-cut sleeves.
The first one will be relatively simple, and the second one will be more difficult.
The first fold-and-cut-sleeve production method is similar to the production method of the white-shoulder group.
First, I need to make the sleeves longer and set an inner line.
Cut the inner line into a seam.
The cut-and-cut board we need to put its side seam point.
The second fold-and-cut board we will introduce on is the left slit and right slit.
The corner they come together will be the left slit.
Now I am going to cut the inner line with the same culling action as thebuzled-line.
You need to align the inner line to the outer line of the board and add points, so that you can identify the number of folds according to the straight line point when using the sewing fold.
After deleting the original sewing line, simulate and fold the board. After hardening, the folding effect will be more obvious.
Then use the sewing fold tool to sew the board.
You can notice that the foldable board of the current sleeve will be stretched.
Here you can notice that the sewing line on the sleeve is equal. This is due to the fact that the board was magnified by 300% by the horizontal ratio before.
The number of internal lines we set is also Samsung N1.
After selecting the sewing line of the foldable board of the sewing line, the sewing line will be re-activated.
After waiting for the foldable board to simulate smoothness, activate the sewing line again.
The foldable board of the sewing line will be stretched.
You can see that the sewing line length of each foldable board is equal.
Therefore, the sleeve will not stretch and the whole will be smoother.
After the foldable board is designed, the sleeve will not shrink.
The sleeve will not be stretched.
The finished sleeve will be aligned to the other side.
Next is the second pleated sleeve.
When making this sleeve, I will first draw the internal pattern as shown in the video, select the internal line and click.
According to the curve, the internal line is set to the number of pleats you want.
After copying the sleeve pattern, select the internal line and cut it off and delete the unnecessary part.
Here, I will first align the bottom line with the left line and cut it and sew it.
Then use the same method to shrink the horizontal portion of the pattern by 300%.
Then select the internal line and set the center of each section separately.
After selecting the sewing line, you can merge the pattern through the sewing line.
Then use the fold-over-folding tool to apply the folding angle of the internal line.
Adjust the weight in the scene to 0 to prevent the pattern from falling down.
After rearranging the pattern, simulate again.
After opening the hardening, the folding effect will be more obvious.
Increase the pattern overall.
After deleting the two internal lines of the original sleeve pattern,
align the remaining internal lines to the outer line of the pattern,
and add points at the same time to divide the lines of the sleeve.
Next, we need to bring the curve of the sleeve to the rectangular pattern we created.
Therefore, here we will use the fold-over tool to select the outer line of the pattern and then fold it into the internal line.
Move the fold-over's internal line to the first internal line and align it.
We can observe the shape of this internal line from the 3D window,
and then continue to use the same method to extract the next internal line,
so that the internal line is visually continuous in the 3D window.
Therefore, we need to draw a horizontal internal line through the part that is folded up in the middle,
and then continue to align the outer line of the sleeve pattern as the internal line.
Next, repeat the same steps to align the shape of the sleeve pattern on the pattern.
We can observe in the 3D window that the movement of this thread is consistent with the outline of the original sleeve pattern.
Select the panel that is folded and align it,
and cut the sheet to delete the unnecessary parts.
But we can see that there are some black bulges on the sheet,
so we need to delete this part of the sheet.
Next, we will see how the front side of the fabric is fixed to the back side of the heat wrap to the back of the heat wrap.
Hello everyone! In this video, I will see the front side of the fabric to be fixed to the back of the heat wrap.
After selecting the outside line of the plate with the hook tool, hook it to the inner line.
After the hook is the inner line, we can zoom in the inner line by pressing ctrl plus 2.
Then select the inner line that intersects with it, increase the point at the intersection, delete the part that exceeds the vertical inner line.
Then press ctrl plus 2 again to paste the inner line of the hook once, select the inner line and delete the triangle area, we can delete the black part of the protrusion.
Then use the same method again to delete all the protruding parts.
Now we can see the inside of the plate.
After the hook is created, select the inner line of the plate and delete the triangle area.
Then we can see the inside of the plate.
Next, we can start sewing the placket.
When we sew this placket, we need to pay attention to prevent the sewing line from crossing in the 3D window.
Sew from the center to both sides to observe the sewing line in the 3D window to avoid crossings.
After the sewing is completed, we need to select all the sewing lines and modify the type of sewing line to Turned.
Turned is the type of sewing line used when the plackets overlap with each other.
Since this part is sewn together by folding the folds, it needs to be used as a placket.
Stick one side of the placket to the other side and sew them together.
We need to arrange the plackets by hand to the model's arm.
Because if we use the arrangement point to arrange the plackets, they will be flattened.
Then use the free-for-all method.
Use the free-for-all method.
Sew the placket and the sleeve together.
When we sew, we need to skip the overlapping part.
Sew the placket to the other side.
Then sew the DAM
The stance of the sleeve is going to be just above the fold.
When we sew, we need to insert the sleeve into the fold part.
When we hit the fold, it's the other way around.
Fed has an oversize molding done.
The futureлениеoresignable.com
Next is the last multi-layer sleeve.
First, use the 3D drawing tool to draw a line on the sleeve to confirm the position of the line.
You can choose the edit dot tool to turn the upper line of the costume into the inner line.
Then I will adjust the curve of the inner line and draw several inner lines again to make a pattern similar to the forest.
In the next step, I will adjust the curve of the inner line to align with thelife line of the costume.
Then lift the inner line of the costume out from the line that will visible on the outside of the costume.
This will make a line on the outside of the costume.
In this part, I will choose the internal line, set the internal line bars on both sides separately, and make a border effect.
We need to align the intersection points to the internal line on which the internal line bars are created.
Set the Perfect Line Depth
Set the Complete Line Depth
I will print the entire line in both lists.
Alright!
After the internal line is completed, we can extract the desired shape.
Here we can first use the collage tool to select the desired area and collage the sheet.
However, we can notice that the collage sheet will create the sheet according to the placement of the 2D window.
Therefore, if we want to extract the sheet from the original position, we can use the collage layer to extract it.
After collaging the sheet to the outside, we can remove the interlocking relationship between the sheets,
and then cut off the internal line,
and only keep the part we need.
Thank you for watching.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
The other part is used to show the relationship of layers.
Then use the free sewing tool to sew the part of the embroidered dragon and embroidered mountain.
When we sew, we need to pay attention to the area with the inner lining that needs to overlap.
Then use the free sewing tool to sew the inner lining that needs to overlap.
We need to use the free sewing tool to sew the inner lining of the dragon.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the inner and outer lines of the overlapping parts together.
Then use the same method to sew the next layer of the board, sewing the outer line of the board together with the overlapping parts of the inner line.
However, when sewing to the end point of the sewing line of the board on the previous layer, it is necessary to continue sewing on the other board.
This is due to the layer relationship of the board sewing.
When sewing, the outer line of the board must be sewn on the inner line.
When sewing, the outer line of the board must be sewn on the inner line of the board.
Next, we need to sew the side seam.
In the 3D window, click on the part of the seam to confirm the location.
We can start sewing from the location of the location to avoid stretching the wrong sewing.
Then we see behind the
Then we use the same method to sew the rest of the sheets one layer at a time.
You can use the selection grid tool to adjust the part of the insertion, and then simulate it.
In the sewing side, you need to ensure that the length of the sewing line is the same, otherwise there will be a stretch.
The correct sewing width is 0.75mm to 0.55mm.
Entire sewing width uses the same length, so you can select the length of the seam.
Two types of sewing, one is 1.1 mm is社이, the other is 1.2 mm is 1.3 mm is 1.4 mm .
Height of estimated sewing width is 2.5 mm.
Suitability of the one-piece sewing width is 1.2 mm.
Thank you.
You